[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Darth Vaders birth name?", "correct_answer": "Anakin Skywalker", "incorrect_answers": ["Han Solo", "Luke Solo", "Luke Skywalker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What island is shared by the nations of Indonesia and Papua New Guinea?", "correct_answer": "New Guinea", "incorrect_answers": ["Bougainville", "Timor", "Borneo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Axel Foley in Beverly Hills Cop is originally a policeman from this city.", "correct_answer": "Detroit", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicago", "Denver", "San Fransisco"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "which of these stories and books have a fox character involved in the storyline?", "correct_answer": "The Adventures of Pinocchio", "incorrect_answers": ["Pippi Longstocking", "The Little Match Girl", "Thumbelina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Steven Spielbergs wife, Kate Capshaw, provided the singing voice of Jessica, the female lead in the movie about Roger Rabbit.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of which major city was Tammany Hall the leading political power brokers?", "correct_answer": "New York", "incorrect_answers": ["Boston", "Detroit", "Chicago"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these great movies was not directed by Frederico Fellini?", "correct_answer": "Farinelli", "incorrect_answers": ["8 and 1/2", "La Dolce Vita", "La Strada"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the city of Athens, Georgia, USA , there is a White Oak tree with more rights than any other tree.  What is so special about this tree?", "correct_answer": "It owns itself.", "incorrect_answers": ["Touching it is against the law.", "It owns a human being.", "It has the right to vote."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Beleaguered castle is a form of what kind of card game?", "correct_answer": "Solitaire", "incorrect_answers": ["Trick taking", "Rummy", "Poker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first evidence of herding behaviour among dinosaurs was discovered in 1878 in which part of the world?", "correct_answer": "Belgium", "incorrect_answers": ["USA", "Argentina", "China"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The sky appears to be blue because of the refraction of light.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The USB memory stick is a very useful device. But do you know what USB stands for?", "correct_answer": "Universal Serial Bus", "incorrect_answers": ["Unique Serial Bus", "Universal Storage Bank", "United Bus Scan"]}]